geekomad.com 2015-12-11

# Privacy Policy | geekOmad - Technology Blog

Below is information regarding geekOmad.com’s commitment to protect the privacy of users and to ensure the integrity of the Internet. This privacy policy is reviewed and revised from time to time. The success of our business depends upon our ability to maintain the trust of our users. If for any reason you have concerns about our software or website’s privacy policies, please contact us. We are committed to ensuring that every user’s needs are addressed. Collection of Personal Information:In the course of delivering this site to you, geekOmad.com does NOT collect any personally-identifiable information about you, such as your name, address, phone number or email address from users of this web site without your knowledge, and are taking measures to protect your privacy. DoubleClick Dart Cookies: Third-party vendors, including Google, also use cookies to serve ads on our website based on a user’s prior visits. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to 

Below is information regarding **geekOmad.com** ’s commitment to protect the privacy of users and to ensure the integrity of the Internet. This privacy policy is reviewed and revised from time to time. The success of our business depends upon our ability to maintain the trust of our users. If for any reason you have concerns about our software or website’s privacy policies, please contact us. We are committed to ensuring that every user’s needs are addressed.

###  **Collection of Personal Information:**

In the course of delivering this site to you, **geekOmad.com** does NOT collect any personally-identifiable information about you, such as your name, address, phone number or email address from users of this web site without your knowledge, and are taking measures to protect your privacy.

**DoubleClick Dart Cookies:** Third-party vendors, including Google, also use cookies to serve ads on our website based on a user’s prior visits. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the advertising opt-out page here ****[Advertising Policies & Principles of Google](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/). 

**Third Party Cookies and Web Beacons:** We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

Additionally, users might be asked to subscribe to our newsletter by providing their name and email address to get access to articles, videos and/or ebooks. We use a secure double opt-in subscription method, and we reserve the right to contact those subscribers with information related to our website. Subscribers may unsubscribe anytime, and every email delivered will contain a link which can be used for that purpose.

You can send email requesting help and your email will NOT be shared in any way with any third party(ies), and will only be used to send replies to you.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this matter, please feel free to [contact us ](http://www.geekomad.com/p/contact.html)
